<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Entrepreneurship on Pawan Kumar</title>
    <link>https://itspawanhere.com/tags/entrepreneurship/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Entrepreneurship on Pawan Kumar</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <copyright>{year}</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 22 Dec 2024 19:00:00 +0530</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://itspawanhere.com/tags/entrepreneurship/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Later-stage Advice for Startups - Lecture by Sam Altman</title>
      <link>https://itspawanhere.com/posts/startup-success-lecture-20/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 22 Dec 2024 19:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>https://itspawanhere.com/posts/startup-success-lecture-20/</guid>
      <description>As a startup grows, the role of the founder evolves from building a great product to building a great company.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Sales and Marketing; How to Talk to Investors - Lecture by Tyler Bosmeny and other YC Partners</title>
      <link>https://itspawanhere.com/posts/startup-success-lecture-19/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 21 Dec 2024 19:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>https://itspawanhere.com/posts/startup-success-lecture-19/</guid>
      <description>There are three segments in this lecture. Tyler Bosmeny, founder and CEO of Clever, starts off the lecture with an overview of the Sales Funnel, and how to get to your first $1 Million.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Legal and Accounting Basics for Startups - Lecture by Kirsty Nathoo and Carolynn Levy</title>
      <link>https://itspawanhere.com/posts/startup-success-lecture-18/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Dec 2024 19:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>https://itspawanhere.com/posts/startup-success-lecture-18/</guid>
      <description>Starting a new company is exciting, but it also comes with a range of legal and financial considerations that can be overwhelming for first-time founders.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Design Hardware Products - Lecture by Hosain Rahman</title>
      <link>https://itspawanhere.com/posts/startup-success-lecture-17/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Dec 2024 19:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>https://itspawanhere.com/posts/startup-success-lecture-17/</guid>
      <description>Designing hardware products, especially wearables, requires a deep understanding of both user needs and technological possibilities.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Run a User Interview - Lecture by Emmett Shear</title>
      <link>https://itspawanhere.com/posts/startup-success-lecture-16/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Dec 2024 19:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>https://itspawanhere.com/posts/startup-success-lecture-16/</guid>
      <description>When you&amp;rsquo;re creating a product, especially for a specific audience, one of the most important things you can do is truly understand your users.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Manage - Lecture by Ben Horowitz</title>
      <link>https://itspawanhere.com/posts/startup-success-lecture-15/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Nov 2024 19:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>https://itspawanhere.com/posts/startup-success-lecture-15/</guid>
      <description>In his lecture, Ben Horowitz, co-founder of Andreessen Horowitz, shared profound insights on one of the most critical aspects of leadership: the ability to understand how decisions are perceived from every point of view within a company.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Operate - Lecture by Keith Rabois</title>
      <link>https://itspawanhere.com/posts/startup-success-lecture-14/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 20 Nov 2024 19:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>https://itspawanhere.com/posts/startup-success-lecture-14/</guid>
      <description>Keith Rabois&amp;rsquo; lecture offers invaluable lessons for anyone navigating the complexities of running a company. From managing people to fostering culture and ensuring operational excellence, Rabois breaks down the art of transforming a fledgling organization into a high-performing machine.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to be a Great Founder - Lecture by Reid Hoffman</title>
      <link>https://itspawanhere.com/posts/startup-success-lecture-13/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 19 Nov 2024 19:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>https://itspawanhere.com/posts/startup-success-lecture-13/</guid>
      <description>Reid Hoffman, co-founder of LinkedIn and a renowned entrepreneur, shared invaluable wisdom in his lecture &amp;ldquo;How to Be a Great Founder.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Building for the Enterprise - Lecture by Aaron Levie</title>
      <link>https://itspawanhere.com/posts/startup-success-lecture-12/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 18 Nov 2024 19:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>https://itspawanhere.com/posts/startup-success-lecture-12/</guid>
      <description>In his insightful lecture titled &amp;ldquo;Building for the Enterprise,&amp;rdquo; Aaron Levie, CEO of Box, shared his journey of building one of the most successful enterprise software companies and offered actionable advice for aspiring entrepreneurs.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hiring and Culture, Part 2 - Lecture by Patrick and John Collison, Ben Silbermann</title>
      <link>https://itspawanhere.com/posts/startup-success-lecture-11/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 17 Nov 2024 19:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>https://itspawanhere.com/posts/startup-success-lecture-11/</guid>
      <description>In a thought-provoking Q&amp;amp;A session, the founders of Stripe and Pinterest shared their wisdom on hiring and building a strong company culture.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Culture - Lecture by Brian Chesky, Alfred Lin</title>
      <link>https://itspawanhere.com/posts/startup-success-lecture-10/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 16 Nov 2024 19:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>https://itspawanhere.com/posts/startup-success-lecture-10/</guid>
      <description>Creating a strong company culture is essential for long-term success, as highlighted by Brian Chesky, founder of Airbnb, and Alfred Lin, former COO of Zappos and current partner at Sequoia Capital.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Raise Money - Lecture by Marc Andreessen, Ron Conway, and Parker Conrad</title>
      <link>https://itspawanhere.com/posts/startup-success-lecture-9/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 15 Nov 2024 19:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>https://itspawanhere.com/posts/startup-success-lecture-9/</guid>
      <description>In this lecture, three successful investors, Marc Andreessen, Founder of Netscape and Andreessen Horowitz, Ron Conway, Founder of SV Angel, and Parker Conrad, Founder of Zenefits, shared their journeys and lessons on building startups.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Get Started, Doing Things that Don&#39;t Scale, Press - Lecture by Stanley Tang, Walker Williams, and Justin Kan</title>
      <link>https://itspawanhere.com/posts/startup-success-lecture-8/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Nov 2024 19:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>https://itspawanhere.com/posts/startup-success-lecture-8/</guid>
      <description>In this lecture, three successful founders, Stanley Tang of DoorDash, Walker Williams of Teespring, and Justin Kan of Twitch, shared their journeys and lessons on building startups.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>How to Build Products Users Love - Lecture by Kevin Hale</title>
      <link>https://itspawanhere.com/posts/startup-success-lecture-7/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 09 Nov 2024 19:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>https://itspawanhere.com/posts/startup-success-lecture-7/</guid>
      <description>Creating a product that people not only use but love involves more than just functional design - it requires crafting an experience that resonates emotionally.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Growth - Lecture by Alex Schultz</title>
      <link>https://itspawanhere.com/posts/startup-success-lecture-6/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Nov 2024 19:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>https://itspawanhere.com/posts/startup-success-lecture-6/</guid>
      <description>In his insightful lecture on growth, Facebook&amp;rsquo;s VP of Growth, Alex Schultz, dives into critical strategies and mindsets that businesses should adopt to achieve sustainable growth.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Competition is for Losers - Lecture by Peter Thiel</title>
      <link>https://itspawanhere.com/posts/startup-success-lecture-5/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Nov 2024 19:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>https://itspawanhere.com/posts/startup-success-lecture-5/</guid>
      <description>Peter Thiel emphasizes the difference between monopolies and perfectly competitive businesses. Unlike competitive markets, where profits are slim due to intense competition, monopolies generate significant wealth by controlling a market.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Building Product, Talking to Users, and Growing - Lecture by Adora Cheung</title>
      <link>https://itspawanhere.com/posts/startup-success-lecture-4/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Nov 2024 21:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>https://itspawanhere.com/posts/startup-success-lecture-4/</guid>
      <description>Adora Cheung, co-founder of Homejoy, shared powerful lessons from her startup experience. Her insights are especially valuable for budding entrepreneurs navigating the challenging path of launching and growing a business.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Before the Startup - Lecture by Paul Graham</title>
      <link>https://itspawanhere.com/posts/startup-success-lecture-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Nov 2024 21:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>https://itspawanhere.com/posts/startup-success-lecture-3/</guid>
      <description>Starting a startup is a journey of learning, challenges, and personal transformation. Here are key takeaways from a lecture by Paul Graham, co-founder of Y Combinator, that shed light on the principles and realities of startup life.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Team and Execution - Lecture by Sam Altman</title>
      <link>https://itspawanhere.com/posts/startup-success-lecture-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Nov 2024 21:00:00 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>https://itspawanhere.com/posts/startup-success-lecture-2/</guid>
      <description>Starting a company is exhilarating but challenging, demanding both strategic and personal resilience. Sam Altman&amp;rsquo;s insights offer practical advice for new entrepreneurs on navigating early-stage challenges.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Unveiling the Essentials of Startup Success</title>
      <link>https://itspawanhere.com/posts/startup-success-lecture-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 May 2024 14:50:07 +0530</pubDate>
      <guid>https://itspawanhere.com/posts/startup-success-lecture-1/</guid>
      <description>Sam Altman and Dustin Moskovitz gave a lecture on &amp;ldquo;How to start a startup&amp;rdquo; in 2014.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
